All right.
He's got a smile for the camera, canned in the pot.
Laughing with the lobbies, giving all that they got.
Bills on the table, want to vanish from sight.
Would just disappear, but he'll sleep well tonight.
Big, beautiful bill, cashing in on our pain.
Got the line points for kids, but his wallet's remade.
Ripping holes in our health, just to sweeten the deal.
Feeding fat cats while we skip another meal.
Slashing through the safety net, scissors in hand
KYC and Medicaid banished on command Telling us it's freedom but the chains are real tight Stacking gold up high while we give up our rights
Empty shelves where our groceries stand.
Empty promises, blood on their hands.
Big, beautiful bill, cashing in on our pain.
Got the lunch for kids, but his wallet's repaying.
Ripping open our health, just to sweeten the deal.
Feeding fat dads while we skip another meal.
So generous.
Take what's there.